eglobaldigitalcameras.com.au 2018-03-15

# Privacy Policy | eGlobal Australia

Last updated: 16/03/2015   

Your privacy is important to eGlobaL. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that eGlobaL collects, and the ways in which eGlobaL uses that personal information.

**Personal information collection**

eGlobaL may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

        information about your use of this website (including to process the order and to deliver the goods ordered);

        information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including customer’s full name, physical address, email address);

        information about transactions carried out over this website (including Credit Card payments other than adopting PayPal gateway); and

        information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including tailored product, promotion and terms and conditions updates);

**Using personal information**

eGlobaL may use your personal information to:

        administer this website;

        personalize the website for you;

        enable your access to and use of the website services;

        display information about you on the website;

        deliver products that you purchase;

        supply to you services that you purchase;

        send you statements and invoices;

        collect payments from you; and

        send you marketing communications.

        share remarketing insights with Google Analytics tool to personalize best marketing offers for you.

**Securing your data**

eGlobaL will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

eGlobaL will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

**Updating this statement**

eGlobaL may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. 

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

**Contact Information**

Privacy Policy Supervisor, eGlobal Digital Cameras

West Wing, 2/F, 822 Lai Chi Kok Road, Lai Chi Kok, Kowloon

e-mail: [privacy@eglobaldigitalcameras.com.au](mailto:privacy@eglobaldigitalcameras.com.au)

**To Unsubscribe**

To close an account, please visit our [online support center](http://www.eglobaldigitalcameras.com.au/contact-us.html) and submit a ticket. Your user account will be closed and all information removed from our server within 48 hours.

To opt-out from our newsletter subscription, please follow the instructions found at the bottom of the newsletter.

To opt-out from our advertising or promotion information, you can unsubscribe [here](http://www.eglobaldigitalcameras.com.au/unsubscribe.php).
